In this section, we're going to discuss retrieval augmented generation or rack.
So we're going to deep dive into 10 key architectural considerations.
You need to keep in mind to build production ready, a rack apps.
So before we deep dive into the architecture, let's understand what is our business use case.
So let's say the CEO of the organization has mandated that every employee in the
organization should learn generative AI.
Now to accomplish that vision, the LND team wants to build an e-learning
generative AI application to accelerate organization learning on emerging AI
technologies.
So in summary, they want to build an e-learning Q&A app.
Now let's say the LND team already has the training content in form of PDFs in
an S3 bucket and it wants us to build a generic app using a rack.
So the functionality of this rack based application should be that they have
multiple AWS engineers who are looking to upskill.
So they should have a chat interface through which they can pose various
questions to help them accelerate their learning.
So the question could be like which bedrock model offers low latency and are
approved in my organization to use. In this scenario, our rack based
application should refer to two PDF documents. One, maybe a bedrock user
guide which talks about all the models that offer low latency.
And the second PDF where it can reference, which are all the approved models
in the organization. So just remember, every organization only white list,
a few subset of models based on their use cases and security requirements.
So once our GenIA app has referenced these two documents, it should be able to
generate a response for our AWS engineer.
So this is the use case. We'll keep in mind, well, building our GenIA app using
a rack. Okay. So that's pretty much it from this lecture.
I'll see in the next lecture. Thank you.